(Sheldon:)because I never went through
a rebellious phase,
(Sheldon:)so, I got an earring.
(Sheldon:)My mother made me
take it out.
(Sheldon:)Amy put alcohol on it.
(Sheldon:)And here we are.
(Howard:)What did we miss?
(Bernadette:)I couldn't explain it
if I tried.
(Penny:)So tell me, how did Sheldon
look with an earring?
(Amy:)Like the pirate who helps
the other pirates
(Amy:)connect to the Internet.
(Howard:)So what did you
and Leonard do?
(Penny:)Actually, we got in
a pretty nasty fight.
(Leonard:)It might've been
the worst one we've ever had.
(Raj:)Oh, my God,
what happened?
(Leonard:)Well, we had started
(Leonard:)binge-watching
Luke Cage together,
(Leonard:)and it was kind of
our thing, and then,
(Leonard:)I find out that she watched
two episodes without me.